<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crew Call on Crew Call | Time Tracking for Film Crew</title><link>https://crewcall.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in Crew Call on Crew Call | Time Tracking for Film Crew</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://crewcall.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://crewcall.xyz/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crewcall.xyz/privacy-policy/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This policy applies to all information collected or submitted via the Crew Call App for iPhone, the Production Hub App for iPadOS and the Production Hub App for macOS.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="1-information-we-collect"&gt;1. Information We Collect&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crew Call collects aggregate, anonymous statistics, such as the percentage of users who use particular features. This information is used to improve Crew Call and guide product development. Data that is collected may include information such as your device&amp;rsquo;s IP address, device name and version, operating system version, your locale, language preferences and other usage statistics.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Terms of Use</title><link>https://crewcall.xyz/terms-of-use/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crewcall.xyz/terms-of-use/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The mobile applications and services available in connection with this mobile application (the “App”) are made available to you by Bradley Andrew (“Developer”, “We”) subject to these Terms of Service, including those set forth in the &lt;a href="https://crewcall.xyz/privacy-policy/"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; (the “Terms”).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By accessing, using or downloading any materials from the App, you agree to follow and be bound by the Terms, which may be updated by us from time to time without notice to you. You can review the most current version of the Terms at any time here. We and third party providers may make improvements and/or changes in the products, services, mobile applications, features, and prices described in this App at any time without notice. Certain provisions of the Terms may be supplemented or superseded by expressly designated legal notices or terms located on particular pages at this App.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://crewcall.xyz/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crewcall.xyz/about/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://crewcall.xyz/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crewcall.xyz/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Crew Call</title><link>https://crewcall.xyz/crew-call/version-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crewcall.xyz/crew-call/version-history/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="version-245"&gt;Version 2.4.5&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introducing Crew Call Documentation! Browse the ‘Docs’ to learn all about Crew Call. Everything from basic usage to advanced functionality is covered. Accessed via the More Tab → Docs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introducing Primary/Secondary Payment Details! Payment Details now correspond with Primary/Secondary Company Details, this allows you to assign different payment info or bank details to invoices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introducing Auto Enable 2nd Meal Break! Work Days will have their 2nd Meal Break enabled by default if the Job uses a Meal Penalty with 2nd Meal Break enabled. This means that Delayed Penalties for 2nd Meal Breaks will now trigger automatically without any additional input. This can be toggled on/off via Settings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where the app could crash when editing a Client in the Invoices Tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id="version-244"&gt;Version 2.4.4&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where ‘Export Daily Times’ wouldn’t show for Work Days that have Logged Locations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where Mileage values wouldn’t update correctly after changing the input of the Mileage Slider.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where Meal Penalty values wouldn’t update correctly after changing the input of the Meal Penalty Slider.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id="version-243"&gt;Version 2.4.3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introducing Skip Days! When adding Multiple Work Days you can select days of the week to skip. This lets you exclude weekends when adding multiple weeks of work at once, handy if you’re working Monday to Friday on a longer job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introducing Export Daily Times! Easily copy the Daily Times for All Working Crew Members to the iOS Clipboard. This lets you quickly send Daily Times to the AD Department. Accessed from the Work Day List, Tap and Hold on a Work Day and select ‘Export Daily Times’.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refined Various UI Elements for iOS 26.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added ‘Tech Scout’ to the list of default values for Pre Production Work Days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added ‘Wrap Out’ to the list of default values for Post Production Work Days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where Work Day values wouldn’t update correctly after changing the input of the Work Day Slider.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where ‘Select Multiple Work Days’ could be selected when a Job had no Work Days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id="version-242"&gt;Version 2.4.2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated Design for iOS 26.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adding or Editing Chargeable Mileage for a Work Day is now more intuitive to prevent accidental dismissals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where the Lock Icon would look squashed in the Work Day List.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where the app could crash while selecting custom dates when converting a Job to an Invoice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Various design tweaks and minor bug fixes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id="version-241"&gt;Version 2.4.1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added ‘Prep Day’ to the list of default values for Pre Production Work Days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where the Contact Us Form would not work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id="version-240"&gt;Version 2.4.0&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Introducing Auto Calculate Mileage! With the tap of a button chargeable mileage for a Work Day can be automatically calculated. Shooting locations, distance from your base radius and travel to accommodation on away jobs is considered. This can be accessed from Notes → Mileage when logging a Work Day. This feature depends on your Base Location, Base Radius, Logged Locations and Home Locations being set for a Work Day, this is accessed from Notes → Locations. Requires iOS 15 or later.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>FAQs</title><link>https://crewcall.xyz/faqs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crewcall.xyz/faqs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Production Hub</title><link>https://crewcall.xyz/production-hub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crewcall.xyz/production-hub/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>